(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-29T23:27:36.462677",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
WAH! Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening! It's me, Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert! I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun sharing all the great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time, but I still get excited
every time I spot something WAHnderful on AmiAmi – it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi on AmiAmi, be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you for everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, Thank you AmiAmi!
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
Ooh~
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
(Let's sing! All for one!)
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(Let's sing! All for one!!)
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion,
Get up and start the celebration,
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see (uh-huh)
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away;
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one.
(Let's sing! All for one!)
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(Let's sing! All for one!)
Keep up the hype, it's good times good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul,
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I'm with you,
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me,
Ooh...
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion,
Get up and start the celebration,
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see, uh-huh
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away;
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
Keep up the hype, it's good times good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul,
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
MYTH -hololive English-
Mori Calliope / Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis
Mori Calliope, Takanashi Kiara, Ninomae Ina'nis
Promise -hololive English-
IRyS / Ouro Kronii / Hakos Baelz
IRyS, Ouro Kronii, Hakos Baelz
ADVENT -hololive English-
Shiori Novella / Koseki Bijou / Nerissa Ravencroft / Fuwawa Abyssgard / Mococo Abyssgard
Shiori Novella, Koseki Bijou, Nerissa Ravencroft, Fuwawa Abyssgard, Mococo Abyssgard
JUSTICE -hololive English-
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame / Gigi Murin / Cecilia Immergreen / Raora Panthera
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame, Gigi Murin, Cecilia Immergreen, Raora Panthera
Welcome to hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE!
Let's start with a bang!
ALL FOR ONE!
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom, my heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud! Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives! Hey!
All that we waited for
The dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion
Get up and start the celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see (uh-huh)
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom, my heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud! Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice singing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives! Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway
Your light will lead our way
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives! Hey!
All that we waited for
The dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Nerissa Ravencroft
Shiori Novella
Koseki Bijou
Fuwawa Abyssgard
Mococo Abyssgard
Turn open your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Living life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is where my story all begins!
Livin' it up like crazy
Ready to play? Come at me
Carried away so easy
I can't get enough!
Free as a bird, no limit
Haven't you heard? I'm fearless
Get up and go, let's do this!
Watch me, watch me, watch me
Watch me be your diva
I'm gonna raise your fever
Shakin' up all the crowd
Making some noise when I'm not allowed
Livin' my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep indulging in my every whim
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Now pay attention, please
'Cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc
How do you like this plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now, woah-oh
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
Gonna start the rave when I misbehave
Take center stage
Let the fun commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense
There are loopholes unspoken
The rules can all be broken
And running on a rampage
The world is a blank page
I'm writing my story
In flames and in glory
They're gonna know me by name!
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hands
But they don't understand
That I'm a star in the making
Awaking and taking a bow-bow-bow-bow
Tell me, how you like me now?
Come watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control
Ready? You got to free your mind
Leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous
The chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is our beginning
It's our genesis!
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now, woah-oh
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Yeah, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
さぁ 散らばってしまった話を
Ah, the stories that have scattered...
空に手を伸ばし始める
Reaching my hands up towards the sky...
知った 通りすぎる曲がった線に
The curved line that passed right by what I knew...
縛られた足をくすぐるの
Tickles my bound feet...
あぁ 落ちて汚れた景色を
Ah, the view that fell and got stained...
今 前途つづつにかけて
Now, betting it all on the journey ahead...
絡みもつれてた体の
Of my body that was tangled up...
夢見ていたまぶたが開く
The eyelids that were dreaming open wide...
心の奥からうごめく記憶が
Memories squirming from deep within my heart...
偽った 呪いと
Curses and...
祈りの
...prayers falsified,
理が 目の前の
...the logic before my eyes...
愛を
...erodes love.
始まる
Toward a starting...
理性に向かって
...sense of reason,
二人に変えていくのは
turning us into two...
神様のような美声だけ
...is only a divine, beautiful voice.
ああ 神様
Ah, God...
そこにいたら教えてほしいの
...if you're there, please tell me.
私が歩くこの道は
This path I walk...
どんな色だろう
...what color is it?
ああ この調べの旋律を
Ah, this melody of notes...
空に向かって伸ばし始める
...begins to reach up toward the sky.
散らばった 多くの血の道標が
Scattered signposts of so much blood...
愛を騙し そして泣き叫んでいる
...deceive love and continue to cry out.
始まる
Toward a starting...
理性に向かって
...sense of reason,
二人に変えていくのは
turning us into two...
神様のような美声だけ
...is only a divine, beautiful voice.
愛しい 祈りの予測を見たら
If I see the prediction of beloved prayers...
教えて
...tell me,
君の手もいつか
will I someday be able...
握れるの？ この...
...to hold your hand in this...?
New York, scream!
You good? You good? You good?
I'm good.
Okay! I'm good!
You good?!
It's finally time!
We're here!
Well, shall we?
We shall. You go first.
I go first?
You go first.
Okay.
You know the drill, guys!
I say WA, you say WA!
WA!
Good morning, afternoon, evening!
This is Ninomae Ina'nis of hololive English...
You got this, you got this!
I just did my song, I'm tired!
Okay! And we have...
WHAT'S UP?!
I am Chaos, the end of days...
...the steel-laced trap in the cage of vice!
Your wild-ride, out-of-bounds, bout-to-take-control...
...of hololive English Promise!
WITNESS ME!
Guys, how was that for an opener?
Did you guys enjoy it?!
I can't hear you!
And of course, everyone watching from home, hello!
We see you guys! We see you! Hello, hello, hello...
We have arrived at...
...the 3rd Concert Live ALL FOR ONE!
Bae, how do you feel?
I feel... fantastic!
Fantastic!
Miraculously preserved.
Yeah, you know...
I can't believe it's already the third live!
First, we Connected the World.
Second, we broke the dimension.
And third...
We are ALL FOR ONE!
Did you guys like... I guess this is the first time we're all together performing "All for One"!
Yeah!
Oh man, I almost cried.
I know! You know I was like... "Oh my God, it's so emotional!"
Ah, but I hope you guys enjoyed the opening that we had, Advent...
...and then we had Ina's solo!
It was so good! Did you guys like it?
All right, you know, since it is the very...
It's the first MC of the first day!
On the first day...
We're just getting started!
We're just getting started! We need to test those penlights!
Yeah, test the penlights! See if they work!
How about we split down the middle here...
And we go purple... Not purple, violet!
It can change color, okay? And violet here...
And red...
And yellow over here! I want to see red!
Oh my goodness! Look at that! Oh my goodness!
Ah, I always get so emotional...
...seeing the sea of penlights!
You know, not only that, we're just getting started.
There's a whole show today and tomorrow.
So make sure to share it with everyone! Share your excitement with #hololiveAllForOne! Post it!
Yay! Tweet it!
Oh man, it's exciting.
Do I get to do the next part? Do I get to do the next part?
Fine, I'll let you do it this time.
Yay! Okay.
Although it is kind of a sad news...
Wait, wait, no, it's just, I've never done it before. I'm really excited, but...
Okay, she's excited, but it's kind of sad because it is now time to announce that...
I have terrible news!
What is it, Hakos Baelz?
Unfortunately, if you are watching from home, this is the end of the free segment!
No!
How could this be? Absolute tragedy! This is a tragedy, but do not worry!
If you are at home and you just saw this bang of an opening, you want to continue watching the rest of the concert,
check the link in the description, get your tickets, and continue watching the concert!
Not you guys! You guys are stuck here until the end!
You're not going anywhere! All right! You guys better be ready with your unlimited energy!
Yeah, I think we should, you know, test a little bit.
Are you guys ready?
Ready!
All right, you know the drill!
Do they know the drill? Do I know the drill?
You know the drill! I know the drill.
All right, countdown from three! Countdown from three! Okay!
Three, two, one...
ALL FOR ONE!
Elizabeth Bloodflame
Cecilia Immergreen
Gigi Murin
Raora Panthera
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[Title: The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.]
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!